Lloyd Wright papers LSC.1561
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 1: Files
  - Project Files
    - Westfair Shopping Center [Martin / Fann] - Shopping Center, Project No. 330
      - Client correspondence (2 of 2) (Box 84, Folder 30)
      - Extras & credits (Box 84, Folder 31)
      - Contractor / owner agreement (Box 84, Folder 32)
      - Grading contract (Box 84, Folder 33)
      - Contractors - vouchers (1 of 2) (Box 84, Folder 34)
      - Contractors (2 of 2) (Box 84, Folder 35)
      - Contractors' certificates - Thrifty (Box 85, Folder 1)
      - Construction - Clerk of the work (Box 85, Folder 2)
      - Shop drawings & samples (Box 85, Folder 3)
      - Contruction - bids (Box 85, Folder 4)
      - Contractor correspondence & data (Box 85, Folder 5)
      - Construction - bids - addenda & revisions (Box 85, Folder 6)
      - Construction - parking data (Box 85, Folder 7)
      - Store requirements - general (Box 85, Folder 8)
      - Specifications - cleaners (Box 85, Folder 9)
      - Specifications - laundry (Box 85, Folder 10)
      - Specifications - barber shop (Box 85, Folder 11)
      - Specifications - beauty parlor (Box 85, Folder 12)
      - Specifications - Baskin Robbins (Box 85, Folder 13)
      - Shop interiors (Box 85, Folder 14)
      - Construction - Safeway Stores Inc. (Box 85, Folder 15)
      - Construction - Thrifty (Box 85, Folder 16)
      - Engineering data (Box 85, Folder 17)
      - Construction - Atlantic Richfield service station (Box 85, Folder 18)
      - Job notes (Box 85, Folder 19)
      - Concrete (Box 85, Folder 20)
      - Billings - general (Box 85, Folder 21)
      - Sign data (1 of 2) (Box 85, Folder 22)
      - Sign data (2 of 2) (Box 85, Folder 23)
      - Specifications - Jan-U-Wine Intl. (Box 85, Folder 24)
      - Specifications (1 of 4) (Box 94, Folder 4)
      - Specifications (2 of 4) (Box 94, Folder 5)
      - Specifications (3 of 4) (Box 94, Folder 6)
      - Specifications (4 of 4) (Box 94, Folder 7)
      - Specifications - Thrifty (1 of 2) (Box 94, Folder 8)
      - Specifications - Thrifty (2 of 2) (Box 94, Folder 9)
      - Specifications - Safeway (Box 94, Folder 10)
      - Specifications - shop interiors (Box 94, Folder 11)
      - Specifications - site development (2 copies) (Box 95, Folder 5)
      - Specifications - shops (1 of 2) (Box 95, Folder 6)
      - Specifications - shops (2 of 2) (Box 95, Folder 7)
      - Specifications - Safeway (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - Westlake Medical Building
      - (1 of 4), Project No. 87 (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - (2 of 4), Project No. 87 (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - (3 of 4), Project No. 87 (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - (4 of 4), Project No. 87 (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - Estimates & specification notes, Project No. 87 (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - Miscellaneous, Project No. 87 (Box 29, Folder 2)
      - Receipts & agreements, Project No. 87 (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - Elevator specifications & data, Project No. 87 (Box 29, Folder 4)
      - Comfort cooling, Project No. 87 (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous data, Project No. 87 (Box 29, Folder 6)
      - Preliminary & original specifications, Project No. 87 (Box 29, Folder 7)
      - Specifications, Project No. 87 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Wood, Beatrice - Residence project
      - Work unit, Project No. 176 (Box 53, Folder 28)
    - World Folk Park - Park, Project No. 313
      - Irwin Parnes (Box 79, Folder 25)
      - Proposal (Box 79, Folder 26)
      - Land lease terms (Box 79, Folder 27)
      - Burbank newspaper clippings, August 1964 (Box 79, Folder 28)
      - Data taken June 16, 1967 (Box 79, Folder 29)
      - Irwin Parnes (Box 79, Folder 30)
      - Balch credit report & miscellaneous publications (Box 79, Folder 31)
      - Budget (Box 79, Folder 32)
      - Clippings (Box 79, Folder 33)
      - Alma Reed (Box 79, Folder 34)
      - Correspondence (Box 79, Folder 35)
      - Moreland Investment Co. (Box 79, Folder 36)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 79, Folder 37)
      - Preliminaries (Box 79, Folder 38)
      - Publications (Box 79, Folder 39)
    - Wright, Gibby L. - Residence, 328
      - Correspondence (Box 86, Folder 29)
      - Client - general (Box 86, Folder 30)
      - Architect's studies (Box 86, Folder 31)
      - Estimates - engineering (Box 86, Folder 32)
      - Specifications (Box 86, Folder 33)
    - Wyle, Frank & Edith - Residential development
      - General, Project No. 161 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Zeitlin, Jake - Book shop
      - General, Project No. 62 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Theatre Design
    - Wright, Lloyd - Theatre
      - Drama, (1 of 2) (Box 93, Folder 25)
      - Drama, (2 of 2) (Box 93, Folder 26)
      - 1920-1926 (Box 93, Folder 27)
- Series 2: Blueprints, plans, drawings, photos, renderings, and other material
  - XXX Bowler, John - Residence 3456 Via Campasinia, Palos Verdes, Calif., 1963, Project No. 303
    Scope and Contents
    Plans/Drawings: Box 561
  - Adams, W.M. - Tule Mat-house Reseda, Calif., 1939, Project No. 118 (Box 223, Box 417)
    Blueprints: Box 223
    Plans/Drawings: Box 417
  - Alexander, Robert - Residence Camino Magento, Thousand Oaks, Calif., 1968, Project No. 331 (Box 266, Box 586)
    Blueprints: Box 266
    Plans/ Drawings: Box 586
  - Aliso Village - Housing Project Los Angeles, 1942, Project No.: 140 (Box 191, Box 193, Box 154, Box 164, Box 185, Box 197, Box 269, Box 435, Box 677)
  - Antaky, Elias - Residence & landscaping Hollywood Hills, 1946, Project No. 162 (Box 455)
    Plans/ Drawings: Box 455
  - Austin Gardens - Gardens Oak Park, Illinois, 1977, Project No. 361 (Box 216, Box 267)
    Blueprints: Boxes 216, 267
  - Avery, Stephen - Residence 365 N. Rockingham Ave., L.A. (Brentwood), 1937, Project No. 102 (Box 218, Box 394)
    Blueprints: Box 218
    Plans/Drawings: Box 394
  - Babcock, Mr. and Mrs. Russell - Residence Mission Cliff Dr., San Diego, Calif., 1953, Project No. 235 (Box 147, Box 245, Box 510, Box 671)
    Blueprints: Boxes 147, 245
    Plans/Drawings: Box 510
    Photos: Box 671
  - Backman, Will D. - Store Ventura Blvd., 1929, Project No. 54 (Box 358)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 358
  - Baer, Hal E. S. - Residence 970 Bel Air Road, no date (Box 158)
    Blueprints: Box 158
  - Barnett - Dog house No address, 1933, Project No. 78 (Box 240, Box 393)
    Blueprints: Box 240
    Plans/Drawings: Box 393
  - Barnsdall Park - Art Center / Gallery Hollywood, 1961 (Box 687)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 687
  - Barnsdall Park - Art Center Hollywood, 1958, Project No. 276 (Box 298)
    Blueprints: Box 298
  - Barnsdall Park - Development by FLW Hollywood, no date (Box 666)
    Other: Box 666
  - Barnsdall Park - Development Hollywood, 1961, Project No. 354 (Box 687)
  - Barnsdall Park - FLW Japanese Print Exhibit Hollywood, no date, Project No. 354 (Box 688)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 688
  - Barnsdall Park - Hollyhock House & Gallery - working drawings Hollywood, 1974-1975 (Box 697)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 697
  - Barnsdall Park - Hollyhock House & Gallery sketches Hollywood, 1974-1975 (Box 696)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 696
  - Barnsdall Park - Hollyhock House remodel - gallery complex, fountains Hollywood, 1969, Project No. 339 (Box 627)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 627
  - Barnsdall Park - Hollyhock House Hollywood, no date, Project No. 368 (Box 674)
    Other: Box 674
  - Barnsdall Park - Hollyhock House Hollywood, no date (Box 299, Box 679)
    Blueprints: Box 299
    Photos: Box 679
  - Barnsdall Park - Japanese Exhibit Hollywood, no date (Box 251)
    Blueprints: Box 251
  - Barnsdall Park - Olive Hill - Residence B Hollywood, no date (Box 679)
  - Barnsdall Park - Theatre in the round studies by FLW Hollywood, 1917-1918 (Box 657)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 657
  - Barnsdall, Aline - Children's outdoor theatre Hollywood, 1931; Project No. 67 (Box 209, Box 179, Box 698, Box 643)
    Blueprints: Boxes 209, 179
    Plans/Drawings: Box 698
    Other: Box 643
  - Barnsdall, Aline - Residence [by Frank Lloyd Wright] Hollywood, no date (Box 664)
    Other: Box 664
  - Barnsdall, Aline - Residence [by Frank LLoyd Wright] Hollywood,1921 (Box 232)
  - Bartfield - Residence Rolling Oaks, Ventura, Calif., 1957, Project No. 258 (Box 177, Box 535, Box 669)
    Blueprints: Box 177
    Plans/Drawings: Box 535
    Other: Box 669
  - Barton, Arthur (landscape architect) - Fremont Park Glendale, 1958 (Box 192)
    Blueprints: Box 192
  - Bassett, J.D. & Dorothy - Cascades Club Palm Springs, Calif., 1934, Project No. 83 (Box 388)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 388
  - Bassett, Mrs. Dorothy - Landscaping 1549 Linda Crest, 1929, Project No. 52 (Box 166, Box 371)
    Blueprints: Box 166
    Plans/Drawings: Box 371
  - Baxter, Anne - Residence remodel 8650 Pine Tree Pl. Los Angeles, 1946, Project No. 167 (Box 277, Box 458)
    Blueprints: Box 277
    Plans/Drawings: Box 458
  - Baxter, Mr. & Mrs. Kenneth - Residence Woodside Hills, San Mateo, Calif., 1947, Project No. 172 (Box 129, Box 461, Box 669)
    Blueprints: Box 129
    Plans/Drawings: Box 461
  - Behn, Harry - Residence Chevy Chase, 1928, Project No. 49 (Box 359)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 359
  - Behn, Harry - Residence Malcolm Ave., Westwood, 1933, Project No. 73 (Box 143, Box 376)
    Blueprints: Box 143
    Plans/Drawings: Box 376
  - Bellenson, Leonard - Residence 410 Capri Drive, Simi Valley, Calif., 1971, Project No. 346 (Box 225, Box 601)
    Blueprints: Box 225
    Plans/Drawings: Box 601
  - Benjamin, L.B. - Residence 8730 Shoreham Dr., 1945, Project No. 154 (Box 133, Box 440)
    Blueprints: Box 133
    Plans/Drawings: Box 440
  - Blalock, Francis - Apartments Alhambra, Calif., 1949, Project No. 191 (Box 145)
    Blueprints: Box 145
  - Blalock, Francis - Residence Los Angeles, 1938, Project No. 112 (Box 409)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 409
  - Block System - Residence Hollywood, 1929, Project No. 37A (Box 605)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 605
  - Boeing Airport - Airfield plot plan Hollywood Way, Burbank, Calif., 1930, Project No. 61 (Box 679, Box 704)
    Other: Box 704
  - Bollman, Henry - Residence Ogden Ave., Los Angeles, 1922, Project No. 10 (Box 127, Box 323, Box 321, Box 334, Box 650)
    Blueprints: Boxes 127, 323, 321
    Plans/Drawings: Boxes 334, 650
  - Bollman, Otto - Residence Hightower Ave., Los Angeles, 1922, Project No. 9 (Box 216)
    Blueprints: Box 216
  - Booth, Sherman M. - Residence elevation by FLW no address, no date (Box 667)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 667
  - Bothwell, Mr. and Mrs. - K & B remodel Ridgeway and Foothill Bl., 1945, Project No. 157A (Box 124, Box 453, Box 645)
    Blueprints: Box 124
    Plans/Drawings: Box 453
    Other: Box 645
  - Bothwell, Murray - Nurse Association 412 W. 6th St., Los Angeles, 1946, Project No. 157B (Box 124)
  - Bowler, John - Residence 3456 Via Campasinia, Palos Verdes, Calif., 1963, Project No. 303 (Box 561, Box 684, Box 671, Box 669)
    Plans/Drawings: Boxes 561, 684
  - Bowler, John - Residence 3456 Via Campasinia, Palos Verdes, Calif., 1963, Project No. 334 (Box 290, Box 584)
    Blueprints: Box 290
    Plans/Drawings: Box 584
  - Brewer, Mrs. Pern - Residence 2221 20th St., Los Angeles, 1945, Project No. 155 (Box 441)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 441
  - Brower, Mrs. Otto - Residence 523 Chapala St., Pacific Palisades, 1937, Project No. 101 (Box 408)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 408
  - Butterworth, Charles - Residence Los Angeles, 1937, Project No. 106 (Box 150, Box 395)
    Blueprints: Box 150
    Plans/Drawings: Box 395
  - Calori, E.E. - Residence Chevy Chase, 1926, Project No. 27 (Box 121, Box 340)
    Blueprints: Box 121
    Plans/Drawings: Box 340
  - Cardenas, Francisco & Mary West - 3-C Ranch Oracle, Pinal County, Arizona, 1945, Project No. 153 (Box 439)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 439
  - Carr, Harold & Alice - Residence Lowry & Rowena, 1925, Project No. 22 (Box 297, Box 337, Box 678)
    Blueprints: Box 297
    Plans/Drawings: Box 337
    Photos: Box 678
  - Carr-Tubb - Residence No address, no date, Project No. no # (Box 222)
    Blueprints: Box 222
  - Carroll, Veda - Residence 5423 Black Oak Drive - N. Beverly Dr., Los Angeles, 1958, Project No. 270 (Box 122, Box 547, Box 669)
    Blueprints: Box 122
    Plans/Drawings: Box 547
  - Cascades Club. Palm Springs, Calif., 1934; Project No. 83 (Box 643)
    General note
    SEE ALSO: McManus
  - Catholic Church - Cathedral Los Angeles, 1931, Project No. 68 (Box 172, Box 610, Box 677)
    Blueprints: Box 172
    Plans/Drawings: Box 610
    Photos: Box 677
  - Chair design Sketch, 1938, Project No. 113 (Box 410)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 410
  - Charles, Ernest - Residence 1210 Benedict Canyon Dr., Beverly Hills, 1948 (Box 469)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 469
  - Chevy Chase - 5 room house no address, 1929 (Box 370)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 370
  - Christian Science - Reading Room Fontana, Calif., 1948, Project No. 186 (Box 287)
    Blueprints: Box 287
  - Christmas card from John Wright No address, 1951 (Box 655)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 655
  - Church of New Jerusalem - Church and apartment Los Angeles, 1965, Project No. 317 (Box 140, Box 571)
    Blueprints: Box 140
    Plans/Drawings: Box 571
  - Colbert, Claudette - Residence 615 N. Faring Rd., 1935, Project No. 91 (Box 209, Box 381, Box 644)
    Blueprints: Box 209
    Plans/Drawings: Box 381
    Other: Box 644
  - Columbia Studios auction poster Hollywood, no date (Box 744)
    Other: Box 744
  - Connell, Will - Furniture & remodel No address, 1934 (Box 379)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 379
  - Connell, Will - Redwood trees 7 photos by Will Connell, 1927 (Box 679)
  - Connell, Will - Residence 335 N. Berendo, Los Angeles, Calif., 1927 (Box 236, Box 380)
    Blueprints: Box 236
    Plans/Drawings: Box 380
  - Connell, Will - Untitled 2 photos, no date (Box 679)
  - Conselman, Will - Residence 4905 Lockhaven, Eagle Rock, Calif., 1927 (Box 208, Box 349)
    Blueprints: Box 208
    Plans/Drawings: Box 349
  - Crandon Park Florida, 1947, Project No. no # (Box 617)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 617
  - Crosby, Floyd - Residence North Hollywood, 1945, Project No. 148 (Box 444)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 444
  - Crosby, Mr. and Mrs. - Residence remodel 53 Empty Saddle Lane, Rolling Hills, Calif., 1978, Project No. 358 (Box 278, Box 624)
    Blueprints: Box 278
    Plans/Drawings: Box 624
  - Crystal Heights by FLW Copies of FLW drawings inscribed to LW from FLW, 1948 (Box 670)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 670
  - Cutler, C.T. - Residence remodel 866 No. Doheny Dr., 1946, Project No. 163 (Box 456)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 456
  - Davis, Alex (architect) - Seaquarium, Marine Science Laboratory Kuwait, 1968 (Box 328)
    Blueprints: Box 328
  - Day, Richard - Residence remodel 2049 Oakstone Way, 1936, 1941, Project No. 95 (Box 127, Box 400)
    Blueprints: Box 127
    Plans/Drawings: Box 400
  - Day, Richard - Residence 2049 Oakstone Way, 1930, Project No. 57 (Box 124, Box 369)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 369
  - Day, Richard - Untitled Lithograph, no date (Box 645)
  - Dean, W.E. - Carport 20717 Malibu Rd., 1947, Project No. 175 (Box 467)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 467
  - Degener, Armin - Residence 1862 Edgemont St., Los Angeles, 1940, Project No. 123 (Box 146, Box 429, Box 703)
    Blueprints: Box 146
    Plans/Drawings: Box 429
    Other: Box 703
  - DeJonghe, Mr. & Mrs. Daniel - Residence Crescent Drive, Hollywood, 1959; Project No. 281 (Box 643)
  - DeJonghe - Residence - "not designed" 9028 Crescent Dr., Los Angeles, 1949; Project No. 195 (Box 143, Box 170, Box 464)
    Blueprints: Boxes 143, 170
    Plans/Drawings: Box 464
  - Dell, George M. - Residence 840 Hanley Ave., Los Angeles, 1953; Project No. 233 (Box 174, Box 257, Box 517)
    Blueprints: Boxes 174, 257
    Plans/Drawings: Box 517
  - DeMille, Cecil B. - Landscape patio gardens Laughlin Park, Los Angeles, no date (Box 628)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 628
  - DeMirjian, E. - Property survey Between Lincoln & 7th, Rose & Machado Dr., 1948; Project No. 193 (Box 466)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 466
  - Demountable housing No address, 1942; Project No. 136 (Box 128, Box 419)
    Blueprints: Box 128
    Plans/Drawings: Box 419
  - Derby, John Daniel - Residence and landscaping 611 Rexford Drive, 1926; Project No. 35 (Box 202, Box 347, Box 677)
    Blueprints: Box 202
    Plans/Drawings: Box 347
  - Dodd, W.J. Altadena, Calif., 1920; Project No. 2
    SEE: - Upham, Frank H. - Landscaping
  - Doheny street widening Beverly Hills, no date (Box 656)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 656
  - Dorland, Allen - Residence 1370 Morada, Altadena, 1949; Project No. 189 (Box 475, Box 643)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 475
  - Duffil, Alma Norton - Residence West Los Angeles, 1948; Project No. 185 (Box 236, Box 478)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 478
  - Dune house North Palm Springs, 1927 (Box 645)
  - Dunham, Lowell - Residence Palos Verdes, Calif., 1958; Project No. 274 (Box 268, Box 543)
    Blueprints: Box 268
    Plans/Drawings: Box 543
  - Eddy, Nelson - Residence 485 Halvern Dr., Brentwood Heights, Calif., 1941; Project No. 130 (Box 422)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 422
  - Edens, Roger - Residence remodel 304 S. Cliffwood Dr., Pacific Palisades, Calif., 1937; Project No. 100 (Box 166, Box 402)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 402
  - El Cerrito - Chapel El Cerrito, Calif., 1951-1955; Project No. 244 (Box 159, Box 671)
    Blueprints: Box 159
    Other: Box 671
  - Elliot - Residence Chevy Chase, 1926; Project No. 29 (Box 342)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 342
  - Ennis, Charles W. - Residence - by Frank Lloyd Wright 2655 Glendower Ave. (1 item only), 1924; Project No. 14 (Box 323)
    Blueprints: Box 323
  - Erickson family - Memorial Minneapolis, Minn., 1965; Project No. 316 (Box 250, Box 572)
    Blueprints: Box 250
    Plans/Drawings: Box 572
  - Erickson Petroleum Corp. - Holiday Service station & order house Minneapolis, Minn., 1964; Project No. 315 (Box 214, Box 572)
    Blueprints: Box 214
  - Erickson, Alfred W. - Residence Edina, Minn., no date; Project No. 202 (Box 673)
    Other: Box 673
  - Erickson, Arthur & Alfred - Residences Parkwood Knolls, Edina, Minnesota, 1950; Project No. 202 (Box 175, Box 273, Box 493)
    Blueprints: Boxes 175, 273
    Plans/Drawings: Box 493
  - Evans, Warwick - Residence 554 Bundy Dr. North, Los Angeles, 1936, 1941; Project No. 99 (Box 205, Box 682)
    Blueprints: Box 205
    Plans/Drawings: Box 682
  - Fairfax Theatre - Theatre Fairfax & Santa Monica, 1926; Project No. 32 (Box 345)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 345
  - Fairmont Hotel - Tower & remodel San Francisco, 1944; Project No. 147 (Box 445)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 445
  - Fann, Martin - Triangle Square Springdale & Warner, Huntington Beach, 1968 (Box 288, Box 290)
    Blueprints: Boxes 288, 290
  - Farrell, Elizabeth - Measured drawing No address, 1982 (Box 322)
    Blueprints: Box 322
  - Farrell - Residence 3209 Lowry Road, 1926; Project No. 36 (Box 222, Box 321)
    Blueprints: Boxes 222, 321
  - Film storage vault No address, 1939; Project No. 121 (Box 433)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 433
  - Fink, David Harold - Residence No address, 1949; Project No. 197 (Box 141, Box 488)
    Blueprints: Box 141
    Plans/Drawings: Box 488
  - First Christian Church - Church - first phase Keats and Avenida de las Flores, Thousand Oaks, 1970; Project No. 342 (Box 188, Box 174, Box 165, Box 171, Box 587, Box 588, Box 589, Box 590, Box 591, Box 706)
    Blueprints: Boxes 188, 174, 165, 171
    Plans/Drawings: Boxes 587, 588, 589, 590, 591
    Other: Box 706
  - First Christian Church - Church Conejo Valley, Calif., 1965; Project No. 320 (Box 174, Box 216, Box 255, Box 318, Box 473, Box 693, Box 672, Box 668)
    Blueprints: Boxes 174, 216, 255, 318
    Plans/Drawings: Boxes 473, 693
    Photos: Box 672
    Other: Box 668
  - FLW exhibit Netherlands, no date (Box 666)
  - Foiltex - Plans for roof remodel No address, [1940] (Box 258, Box 622)
    Blueprints: Box 258
    Plans/Drawings: Box 622
  - Forestry conservation study Maps & notes, 1945 (Box 646)
    Blueprints: Box 646
  - Forsch, Charles - Residence 942 N. La Jolla, Los Angeles, Project No. 149 (Box 443)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 443
  - Foun Square Housing Los Angeles, 1939; Project No. 119 (Box 235, Box 416)
    Blueprints: Box 235
    Plans/Drawings: Box 416
  - Frank Lloyd Wright - 1937 photograph by E. Teske Copy print, no date (Box 674)
    Photos: Box 674
  - Frank Lloyd Wright - Exhibition and lecture posters no address, no date (Box 643)
  - Frank Lloyd Wright - Photo By E. Teske, 1937 (Box 675)
    Photos: Box 675
  - Freeman, Helen - Office block No address, no date (Box 613)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 613
  - Freeman, Samuel - Residence - design by FLW, landscaping by LW 1962 Glencoe Way, 1924 (Box 321)
    Blueprints: Box 321
  - Freeman, Samuel - Residence - design by FLW, landscaping by LW 1962 Glencoe Way, 1924; Project No. 15 (Box 321, Box 323, Box 331)
    Blueprints: Boxes 321, 323
    Plans/Drawings: Box 331
  - Furthman, Jules - Residence Bel Air, Calif., 1932; Project No. 70 (Box 136, Box 375)
    Blueprints: Box 136
    Plans/Drawings: Box 375
  - Gage, Lyman - Landscaping Bailey's Canyon, no date; Project No. 8 (Box 642)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 642
  - Gainsburg, Mr. & Mrs. Emanuel - Residence, garage & landscape 1210 Journey's End Dr., La Canada, Calif., 1946; Project No. 169 (Box 192, Box 460)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 460
  - Galt, Randolph - Giro station Australia, 1961; Project No. 366 (Box 606)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 606
  - Geritz, Franz - [Untitled] Prints & etchings, no dates (Box 645)
  - Get well card from "Bill", no date (Box 655)
    Other: Box 655
  - Gilkerson, Dr. J.K. - Landscape Chevy Chase, Calif., 1925; Project No. 21 (Box 218, Box 336, Box 707)
    Plans/Drawings: Boxes 336, 707
  - Good Shepherd Community Church - Church Des Plaines, Illinois, 1957; Project No. 262 (Box 139, Box 270, Box 283, Box 284, Box 530, Box 545, Box 673)
    Blueprints: Boxes 139, 270, 283, 284
    Plans/Drawings: Boxes 530, 545
    Photos: Box 673
  - Good Shepherd Community Church - Church Ballard Gardens, Cook County, Ill., 1957; Project No. 272 (Box 120, Box 533)
    Blueprints: Box 120
    Plans/Drawings: Box 533
  - Gracy, David - Residence Austin, Texas, 1937; Project No. 103 (Box 407)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 407
  - Greer, Howard - Dressmaking plant 8446 W. 3rd St., Los Angeles, 1945 Sept.; Project No. 156 (Box 472)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 472
  - Greer, Howard - Residence & additions 9200 Haskell Ave., 1948; Project No. 184 (Box 289, Box 474)
    Blueprints: Box 289
    Plans/Drawings: Box 474
  - Greer, Howard - Residence additions 9200 Haskell Ave., 1945; Project No. 152 (Box 437)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 437
  - Greer, Howard - Residence 9200 Haskell Ave., 1940; Project No. 128 (Box 275, Box 425)
    Blueprints: Box 275
    Plans/Drawings: Box 425
  - Greer, Howard - Sketch of room interior No address, no date (Box 644)
  - Griffith, Raymond - Residence Laughlin Park, 1935; Project No. 92 (Box 396, Box 644)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 396
  - Griffith, Raymond - Residence 2965 Rigoletto St., Canoga Park, Calif., 1936; Project No. 94 (Box 151, Box 397)
    Blueprints: Box 151
    Plans/Drawings: Box 397
  - Griffith, Raymond - Yucca Vine Market Hollywood, 1928; Project No. 51 (Box 240, Box 350, Box 677)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 350
  - Group housing sketches by FLW No address, no date (Box 662)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 662
  - H., M.B., Mr. & Mrs. - Landscaping No address, 1925; Project No. 23 (Box 625)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 625
  - Haight, George - Residence remodel 613 N. Beverly Dr., Beverly Hills, Calif., 1939; Project No. 116 (Box 414)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 414
  - Haight, George - Residence 1850 Sunset Plaza Dr., Los Angeles, 1937; Project No. 107 (Box 201, Box 404)
    Blueprints: Box 201
    Plans/Drawings: Box 404
  - Halfhill, H.J. - Apartments No address, 1932; Project No. 72 (Box 372)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 372
  - Hamilton / Hazeltine, W. - Chicago River Etching, no date (Box 645)